{
  "heading": "Singular and Plural.",
  "topics": [
    {
      "heading": "Singular and Plural",
      "questions": [
        {
            "questionNo": 1,
            "question": "Which is singular?",
            "options": [
                "Leaves",
                "Trees",
                "Branch"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 2,
            "question": "Which is plural?",
            "options": [
                "Goose",
                "Moose",
                "Geese"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 3,
            "question": "One fox, two ______.",
            "options": [
                "foxs",
                "foxes",
                "fox"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 4,
            "question": "One monster, two ______.",
            "options": [
                "monsters",
                "monster",
                "monsteres"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 5,
            "question": "My monster has one eye, but some monsters have many ______.",
            "options": [
                "eyes",
                "eye",
                "eyez"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 6,
            "question": "The monster has one arm, but another has six ______.",
            "options": [
                "armes",
                "arms",
                "armz"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 7,
            "question": "One colour, many ______.",
            "options": [
                "colour",
                "coloures",
                "colours"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 8,
            "question": "Which is plural?",
            "options": [
                "Pizza",
                "Slice",
                "Pizzas"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 9,
            "question": "One big teacup, two big ______.",
            "options": [
                "teacup",
                "teacups",
                "teacupes"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 10,
            "question": "The monster has one special power, but some have many ______.",
            "options": [
                "special powers",
                "special poweres",
                "special powerz"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 11,
            "question": "Fill in the blank:<br> One funny shape, many funny ______.",
            "options": [
                "shape",
                "shapes",
                "shapies"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 12,
            "question": "Which is singular?",
            "options": [
                "Features",
                "Arms",
                "Silly"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 13,
            "question": "One adventure, many ______.",
            "options": [
                "adventure",
                "adventures",
                "adventurez"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 14,
            "question": "Fill in the blank:<br> One _____, many stories.",
            "options": [
                "story",
                "storey",
                "storie"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 15,
            "question": "One big letter, many big ______.",
            "options": [
                "letters",
                "letter",
                "letteres"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 16,
            "question": "Which is plural?",
            "options": [
                "Game",
                "Favourite",
                "Powers"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 17,
            "question": "The monster has one nose, but some have three ______.",
            "options": [
                "nose",
                "noses",
                "nosees"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 18,
            "question": "Which is singular?",
            "options": [
                "Pet",
                "Monsters",
                "Eyes"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 19,
            "question": "Fill in the blank:<br> One _____, many children.",
            "options": [
                "child",
                "children",
                "childs"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 20,
            "question": "Fill in the blank:<br> One monster _____, many monsters eat.",
            "options": [
                "eates",
                "eats",
                "eaten"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ]
    
    
    
    }
  ]
}
